tvgamedepot.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Tv game Depot

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tvgamedepot **.com** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a “User”).

Privacy  
Users. privacy is very important to Tvgamedepot **.com**. Tvgamedepot **.com** is committed to safeguarding and protecting the information Users entrust to Tvgamedepot **.com**. This Web site is not directed at children under 18 years of age.

The Information We Collect  
Tvgamedepot **.com** may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms, registration, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Tvgamedepot **.com** may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users. PC or computer and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

How We Use Information  
Tvgamedepot **.com** may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Tvgamedepot **.com** and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users. experience with Tvgamedepot **.com** and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Tvgamedepot **.com** may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Tvgamedepot **.com** , its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners; for example, to provide you with information about products which might be of interest to you or to enable you to take advantage of special partner programs or Tvgamedepot **.com** specials. When you sign up to the Tvgamedepot **.com** website you are opting in to our monthly news letter. Tvgamedepot **.com** may also use customer information to provide customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products.

Disclosure of Information  
Tvgamedepot **.com** may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of Tvgamedepot **.com** ’s business.

Maintenance of Information  
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry or above industry standards in security tactics. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

Questions  
Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to admins @ Tvgamedepot **.com** **.com**.

Users may choose not to receive any type of solicitations from Tvgamedepot **.com** or from any of its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and or business partners by emailing us at admins @ Tvgamedepot **.com**
